DUDE
WHAT ARE YOUR
THOUGHTS ON THE
THREE REMAINING
UNDEFEATED NFL TEAMS
I THINK THAT
THE CHIEFS ARE
OBVIOUSLY PLAYING
GOOD
KENNETH WALKER IS
A DOG
DUDE
THAT ADDITION TO
KENNETH WALKER
THEIR RUN GAME
IS PHENOMENAL
I KNOW HE'S
RUSHED FOR OVER
150 YARDS PER
GAME
I FEEL LIKE
AND IT JUST
OPENS UP THEIR
PASS GAME SO
WELL
I KNOW
THEY DON'T HAVE
THOSE SAME WEAPONS
AND RECEIVERS THEY
DO NOW OR
THEY USED TO
HAVE
BUT KENNETH WALKER
IS A GREAT
ADDITION TO THAT
CHIEFS
YEAH
VIKINGS
I MEAN
I HEARD SOMETHING
LAST NIGHT
LIKE THEY HAVEN'T
SCORED A TOUCHDOWN
IN 32 DRIVES
SO IT'S BEEN
A STRAIGHT FIELD
OKAY
NO
BUT I THINK
KYLER MURRAY IS
REALLY STARTING
TO SETTLE IN
YOU'VE SEEN THAT
IN THE SECOND
HALF YESTERDAY WATCHING
THAT GAME
THAT KYLER'S REALLY
STARTING TO SETTLE
IN
HE MADE A
LOT OF HIS
GOOD PASSES
SMART READS
AND OBVIOUSLY
THAT DEFENSE IS
JUST PHENOMENAL
AMAZING
AND IT'S HARD
BECAUSE JUSTIN JEFFERSON'S
BEEN OUT FOR
THE PAST TWO
GAMES
JORDAN MASON
THEY HAD A
FEW OFFENSIVE LINEMEN
GO DOWN YESTERDAY
THEY ADJUSTED WELL
AND PLAYED PRETTY
GOOD FOOTBALL
BUT THE NINERS
BROCK PURDY
MVP
BABY
I KNOW
MAN
I MEAN
IT'S JUST LIKE
THE NINERS WERE
NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE WHAT THEY
ARE
YEAH
AND LIKE NOW
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY
JUST CRUSHING RUSHING
TEAMS
I THINK THEIR
POINT DIFFERENTIAL
IS THE BEST
IN THE LEAGUE
YEAH
IT'S LIKE 59
OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT
LIKE PLUS 59
AND THEY PLAYED
GOOD TEAMS
TOO
YEAH
LIKE THEY PLAYED
THE RAMS
I DON'T REMEMBER
WHO THEY WERE
TOO
LIKE THEY BEAT
UP ON THE
BRONCOS
YEAH
THE NINERS ARE
LOOKING GOOD
MAN
YEAH
I'M SCARED
VIKINGS ARE NOT
WINNING THE NFC
WITH THE NINERS
THEY'RE GOING TO
KEEP PLAYING THIS
WAY